<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Chaire Design Jean Prouvé</title>
    <link>https://chaire-design.fr/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Chaire Design Jean Prouvé</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>CNAM.design</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 00:55:28 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chaire-design.fr/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Médiums en design</title>
      <link>https://chaire-design.fr/en/seminar/mediums-en-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 16:30:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaire-design.fr/en/seminar/mediums-en-design/</guid>
      <description>À l’occasion de la création de la Chaire Design Jean Prouvé au CNAM et de CY Ecole de Design nous sommes heureux de vous annoncer le lancement d’un séminaire commun ouvert à tous : « les Médiums en design : pour une anthropologie symétrique du design ».
En repartant du texte fondateur de Donald Schön sur la « conversation réflexive avec les matériaux » (Schön,1992), nous vous proposons de discuter de la variété et de l’agentivité des médiums du design et de la façon dont le designer fait sens des matières au sein de sa pratique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pierre Lévy</title>
      <link>https://chaire-design.fr/en/team/pierre_levy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Dec 2020 16:30:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaire-design.fr/en/team/pierre_levy/</guid>
      <description>Pierre Lévy is professor at the National Conservatory of Arts and Crafts (CNAM) in France, holder of the Chair of Design Jean Prouvé, and researcher at the Dicen-IDF lab. He is interested in the correspondence between theories and design practices, especially regarding transforming practices and sciences. His research mainly focuses on embodiment theories and Japanese philosophy and culture in relation to designing for the everyday. He holds a Mechanical Engineering master’s degree (UT Compiègne, France), a doctoral degree in Kansei (affective) Science (University of Tsukuba, Japan), and a HDR in Information and Communication Sciences (UT Compiègne, France).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Chaire Jean Prouvé</title>
      <link>https://chaire-design.fr/en/about/creation-chaire-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 13:00:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaire-design.fr/en/about/creation-chaire-design/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
